[
  { "question": "mountain (n)\n /ˈmaʊn.tɪn/", "answer": "ngọn núi" },
  { "question": "hill (n)\n /hɪl/", "answer": "đồi" },
  { "question": "valley (n)\n /ˈvæl.i/", "answer": "thung lũng" },
  { "question": "plain (n)\n /pleɪn/", "answer": "đồng bằng" },
  { "question": "river (n)\n /ˈrɪv.ər/", "answer": "sông" },
  { "question": "stream (n)\n /striːm/", "answer": "dòng suối" },
  { "question": "lake (n)\n /leɪk/", "answer": "hồ" },
  { "question": "pond (n)\n /pɒnd/", "answer": "ao" },
  { "question": "waterfall (n)\n /ˈwɔː.tə.fɔːl/", "answer": "thác nước" },
  { "question": "ocean (n)\n /ˈəʊ.ʃən/", "answer": "đại dương" },
  { "question": "sea (n)\n /siː/", "answer": "biển" },
  { "question": "beach (n)\n /biːtʃ/", "answer": "bãi biển" },
  { "question": "coast (n)\n /kəʊst/", "answer": "bờ biển" },
  { "question": "island (n)\n /ˈaɪ.lənd/", "answer": "hòn đảo" },
  { "question": "forest (n)\n /ˈfɒr.ɪst/", "answer": "khu rừng" },
  { "question": "jungle (n)\n /ˈdʒʌŋ.ɡl̩/", "answer": "rừng rậm" },
  { "question": "desert (n)\n /ˈdez.ət/", "answer": "sa mạc" },
  { "question": "cave (n)\n /keɪv/", "answer": "hang động" },
  { "question": "cliff (n)\n /klɪf/", "answer": "vách đá" },
  { "question": "volcano (n)\n /vɒlˈkeɪ.nəʊ/", "answer": "núi lửa" },
  { "question": "glacier (n)\n /ˈɡlæ.si.ər/", "answer": "sông băng" },
  { "question": "rock (n)\n /rɒk/", "answer": "tảng đá" },
  { "question": "stone (n)\n /stəʊn/", "answer": "hòn đá" },
  { "question": "sand (n)\n /sænd/", "answer": "cát" },
  { "question": "soil (n)\n /sɔɪl/", "answer": "đất" },
  { "question": "earth (n)\n /ɜːθ/", "answer": "trái đất, đất" },
  { "question": "grass (n)\n /ɡrɑːs/", "answer": "cỏ" },
  { "question": "tree (n)\n /triː/", "answer": "cây" },
  { "question": "bush (n)\n /bʊʃ/", "answer": "bụi cây" },
  { "question": "flower (n)\n /ˈflaʊ.ər/", "answer": "hoa" },
  { "question": "leaf (n)\n /liːf/", "answer": "lá cây" },
  { "question": "root (n)\n /ruːt/", "answer": "rễ cây" },
  { "question": "branch (n)\n /brɑːntʃ/", "answer": "cành cây" },
  { "question": "sky (n)\n /skaɪ/", "answer": "bầu trời" },
  { "question": "cloud (n)\n /klaʊd/", "answer": "đám mây" },
  { "question": "rain (n)\n /reɪn/", "answer": "mưa" },
  { "question": "snow (n)\n /snəʊ/", "answer": "tuyết" },
  { "question": "fog (n)\n /fɒɡ/", "answer": "sương mù" },
  { "question": "wind (n)\n /wɪnd/", "answer": "gió" },
  { "question": "storm (n)\n /stɔːm/", "answer": "bão" },
  { "question": "lightning (n)\n /ˈlaɪt.nɪŋ/", "answer": "tia sét" },
  { "question": "thunder (n)\n /ˈθʌn.dər/", "answer": "tiếng sấm" },
  { "question": "rainbow (n)\n /ˈreɪn.bəʊ/", "answer": "cầu vồng" },
  { "question": "sun (n)\n /sʌn/", "answer": "mặt trời" },
  { "question": "moon (n)\n /muːn/", "answer": "mặt trăng" },
  { "question": "star (n)\n /stɑːr/", "answer": "ngôi sao" }
]
